Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series II (Box 49)
  - International Labor Defense
    - "You Cannot Kill ...," Herndon, Angelo, undated. (Folder 95: 8)
    - "Lynching Negro ...," North, Joseph, undated. (Folder 95: 9)
    - "Sacco and Vanzetti ...," Shachtman, Max, 1927. (Folder 95: 10)
    - "Scottsboro" and "Hell in Georgia ...," Small, Sasha, 1934-1935. (Folder 95: 11)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
    - Claessens, August
      - "ABC of Parliamentary Law with Rebecca E. Jarvis,", 1936. (Folder 95: 12)
      - "A Manual for Trade Union Speakers,", 1936. (Folder 95: 13)
        Brief text book
    - "Handbook of Trade ...,", 1937. (Folder 95: 14)
    - "You and Your Union,", 1935. (Folder 95: 15)
  - International Longshoremens' and Warehousemens' Union--"Report from ...," Bridges, Harry, 1949. (Folder 95: 16)
  - International Pamphlets
    - "On the Chain Gang," Spivak, John L., 1932 (Folder 95: 17)
    - "Dictatorship and Democracy in the Soviet Union," Strong, Anna Louise, 1934 (Folder 95: 18)
    - "NRA from Within," Thompson, William O., and Mary van Kleeck, and "The Communist Position," Browder, Earl, 1934 (Folder 95: 19)
  - International Publishers/Pamphlets
    - "The American Negro," Allen, J. S., 1932. (Folder 95: 20)
    - "The Constitution of the United States," Browder, Earl, 1937. (Folder 95: 21)
    - "A Southerner Looks ...," Cable, George W., 1946. (Folder 95: 22)
      Selected writings
    - "Science and Religion," Cachin, Marcel, 1946. (Folder 95: 23)
    - "France Faces Her Destiny," Duclos, Jacques, 1946. (Folder 95: 24)
    - "The Palmer Raids," edited by Dunn, Robert W., 1948. (Folder 95: 25)
    - "The British Labour Movement," Engels, Frederick, 1940. (Folder 95: 26)
    - "To American Intellectuals," Gorky, Maxim, 1932. (Folder 95: 27)
    - "Lynching," Haywood, H., and M. Howard, 1932. (Folder 95: 28)
    - "One of the 25,000," Isbach, A., undated. (Folder 95: 29)
    - "Marxism and Modern Art," Klingender, F. J., 1945. (Box-folder 96: 1)
    - "300 Million Slaves and Serfs ...," Kuczynski, Jürgen, 1943. (Folder 96: 2)
    - "Karl Marx: His Life and Work," Lafargue, Paul, and Wilhelm Liebknecht, 1943. (Folder 96: 3)
    - "The Paris Commune," Lenin, V. I., 1934. (Folder 96: 4)
    - "Religion," Lenin, V. I., 1933. (Folder 96: 5)
    - "Marxism and Revisionism," Lenin, V. I. and Joseph Stalin, 1946. (Folder 96: 6)
    - "Battle for America ...," Magil, A. B., 1943. (Folder 96: 7)
    - "The Communist Manifesto," Marx, Karl, and Friedrich Engels, 1932. (Folder 96: 8)
    - "Toward a Land of Plenty," Mikoyan, A. I., 1936. (Folder 96: 9)
    - "Monopoly in the United States,", 1942. (Folder 96: 10)
    - "William Z. Foster," North, Joseph, 1955. (Folder 96: 11)
    - "Karl Marx," Perchik, L., 1934. (Folder 96: 12)
    - "Toward Singing Tomorrows ...," Aragon, Louis, 1946. (Folder 96: 13)
    - "The Materialist Conception of History," Plekhanov, George, 1940. (Folder 96: 14)
    - "Political Economy in the Soviet Union,", 1944. (Folder 96: 15)
    - Political Education.
      - "The Two Worlds," Part I, 1935 (Folder 96: 16)
      - "The Ultimate Aim," Part II, 1935 (Folder 96: 17)
      - "The Communist Party," Part III, 1935 (Folder 96: 18)
    - "José Marti and Cuban Liberation, Rodrigues, Carlos Rafael, 1953. (Folder 96: 19)
    - "Lenin on the Soviet State, Stetsky, A. I., 1935. (Folder 96: 20)
  - International Union of Students--"Independence Now!", 1970. (Folder 96: 21)
  - The League for the Liberation--"Conscience: The Strange Way ...,", undated. (Folder 96: 22)
  - International Publishers
    - Stalin, Joseph
      - "The World Situation ...,", 1934. (Folder 96: 23)
      - "Dialectical ...,", 1940. (Folder 96: 24)
      - "Economic Problems ...,", 1952. (Folder 96: 25)
      - "For Peaceful Co-existence: Post-war Interviews,", 1951. (Folder 96: 26)
      - "From Socialism to Communism ...,", 1939. (Folder 96: 27)
      - "Marxism vs. ...," with Wells, H. G., 1935. (Folder 96: 28)
    - "The History of May Day," Trachtenberg, Alexander, 1935. (Folder 96: 29)
    - "Socialism and War ...," Zinoviev, G., and V. I. Lenin, 1930. (Folder 96: 30)
  - International Trade Union Educational League--"Trade Unionism ...," Foster, William Z., undated. (Folder 96: 31)
  - International Trade Union Committee of Negro Workers--"Negro Workers and the Imperialist War ...," Padmore, George, 1931. (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers--"Current Legislation ...,", undated. (Folder 97: 2)
  - International Union of Students
    - "Foe Anti-Imperialist Solidarity ...,", 1998. (Folder 97: 3)
    - "Resolutions of the 11th IUS Congress,", 1974. (Folder 97: 4)
    - "This Is the I.U.S.,", 1950. (Folder 97: 5)
    - "The University and ...,", 1972. (Folder 97: 6)
      Seminar proceedings
    - "The University and Science ...,", 1972. (Folder 97: 7)
    - "U.S. Education in Crisis,", 1950. (Folder 97: 8)
    - "The World Festival of Youth ...,", 1972. (Folder 97: 9)
  - International Workers of the World?--"The I.W.W. Prisoners,", 1922. (Folder 97: 10)
  - International Workers Order--"Century of the Common Man," Wallace, Henry A., 1943. (Folder 97: 11)
  - Inter-Religious Committee for Justice for Thomas F. Moody--"Our American Dreyfus Case ...," Symes, Lillian, 1935. (Folder 97: 12)
  - Investigating Committee for Free Jurists--"Ex-Nazis in the Service ...,", undated. (Folder 97: 13)
  - Irving Kaye Davis and Company--"Debs Goes to Prison," Karsner, David, 1919. (Folder 97: 14)
  - Israel Information Services
    - "The Record of Aggression,", 1967. (Folder 97: 15)
    - "Arab Terror Strategy ...," Tekoah, Yosef, 1968?. (Folder 97: 16)
      Excerpts from addresses
    - "Where Arab and Jew Meet ...,", 1968. (Folder 97: 17)
  - Israel Ministry for Foreign Affairs
    - "Israel Policy Statements," Meir, Golda, 1970. (Folder 97: 18)
      Address to the Knesset
    - "The Jewish Exodus From ...,", undated. (Folder 97: 19)
    - "Mideast Focus: No ...,", 1969. (Folder 97: 20)
  - Joseph L. Warner, "The Association of ...,", 1921. (Folder 97: 21)
  - J. Thomas and Company--"The Truth About ...," Bass, George, Mrs., undated. (Folder 97: 22)
  - Jack B. Tenney, "Let's Try Freedom ...,", 1954. (Folder 97: 23)
  - Jackson, B. F., "The Mystery of the Serpent ...," Book I, undated. (Folder 97: 24)
  - Jackson, Ricou, "The Tragic Truth ...,", 1962. (Folder 97: 25)
  - Jamax Books--"Black Tide," Pierce, Julius A., 1963. (Folder 97: 26)
  - James S. Kemper, "Law and Order,", 1965. (Folder 97: 27)
  - James Oviatt, "Files Suit for ...,", 1964?. (Folder 97: 28)
  - "Jersey Justice at Work ...,", 1913. (Folder 97: 29)
  - Jewish Life
    - "Soviet Anti-Semitism ...," Miller, Moses, undated. (Folder 97: 30)
    - "Resistance Is the Lesson ...," Schappes, Morris U., 1948. (Folder 97: 31)
  - Jewish National Fund--"Land for Jewish Settlement ...,", undated. (Folder 97: 32)
  - Jewish War Veterans of the USA--"The John Birch Society ...,", 1965. (Folder 97: 33)
  - Jews for Jesus, 1971. (Folder 97: 34)
  - John Birch Society
    - Allen, Gary
      - "Bad Medicine ...,", 1971. (Folder 97: 35)
      - "The Bankers and the Federal Reserve,", 1970. (Folder 97: 36)
      - "The C.F.R. ...,", 1969. (Folder 97: 37)
      - "The Unelected,", 1968. (Folder 97: 38-39)
        Article (One folder empty)
      - "Las Uvas ...,", 1966. (Folder 97: 40)
      - "New Education: The Radicals ...,", 1971. (Folder 97: 41)
      - "Public Schools,", 1972. (Folder 97: 42)
      - "Shortages: The Politics ...,", 1973. (Box-folder 98: 1)
      - "Vitamins: Federal ...,", 1973. (Folder 98: 2)
      - "War on Poverty ...,", 1967. (Folder 98: 3)
      - "Who Controls the Press?", 1970. (Folder 98: 4)
      - "Your Home,", 1973. (Folder 98: 5)
    - "Drugs and Youth: The De-Generation ...," Avery, Dave, undated. (Folder 98: 6)
    - Bulletin for May, 1960 (Folder 98: 7)
    - "Since F.D.R. ...," Capell, Frank A., 1971. (Folder 98: 8)
    - "The UN Threat to the US," Chamberlin, William Henry, undated. (Folder 98: 9)
    - Charter of the United Nations, undated. (Folder 98: 10)
    - "Civil Rights ...,", undated. (Folder 98: 11)
    - "The UN: A Study ...," Conner, Stillwell John, 1963. (Folder 98: 12)
    - "The Rape of Yale," Dedman, Julien, 1969. (Folder 98: 13)
    - "Pornography: Mindless ...," Evans, Medford, 1969. (Folder 98: 14)
    - "The Treason of the Churches," Fenton, Francis E., 1972. (Folder 98: 15)
    - Gumaer, David E.
      - "Apostasy and the ...,", 1970. (Folder 98: 16)
      - "Satanism: A Practical Guide ...,", 1970. (Folder 98: 17)
    - Huck, Susan L. M.
      - "Insurrection: Is America ...,", 1968. (Folder 98: 18)
      - "Renegades: The Second ...,", 1973. (Folder 98: 19)
    - "Color, Communism ...," Johnson, Manning, 1917. (Folder 98: 20)
    - "An Overview of Our World ...," McManus, John F., 1971. (Folder 98: 21)
      Presentation based on a lecture
    - "Pre-Trial Mental Examination: A Dread Weapon," and "Mindtapping ...," Morris, Robert, 1962. (Folder 98: 22)
    - "On the Differences between ...,", 1961. (Folder 98: 23)
    - "Report of the American Bar Association ...,", 1958. (Folder 98: 24)
    - "Sex and Love ...," Root, E. Merrill, undated. (Folder 98: 25)
    - "Disarmament," Rousselot, John, 1963. (Folder 98: 26)
    - "Why I Ran for President ...," Schmitz, John G., 1972. (Folder 98: 27)
    - "The Captives ...," Shields, Rose Beverage, 1967. (Folder 98: 28)
    - "The Fall from Democracy ...," Schuyler, George S., 1969. (Folder 98: 29)
    - Stang, Allen
      - "Canada" (Folder 98: 30)
      - "Food Prices ...,", 1973. (Folder 98: 31)
      - "Forced Blessing ...,", 1971. (Folder 98: 32)
      - "OSHAcrats,", 1972. (Folder 98: 33)
      - "The Child Care Bill,", 1975. (Folder 98: 34)
      - "The N.E.A. ...,", 1972. (Folder 98: 35)
    - "Stop ... Look ... and Listen,", undated. (Folder 98: 36)
      Statistical report
    - "Support your Local Police,", 1963. (Folder 98: 37)
    - The John Birch Resolutions (Folder 98: 38)
    - "Why We Must Keep America's Canal ...," Thomson, Meldrim, Jr., 1977. (Folder 98: 39)
    - "Help! Save the Panama Canal," Varney, Harold Lord, 1965. (Folder 98: 40)
    - Welch, Robert
      - "A Brief Introduction to the John Birch Society,", 1962. (Folder 98: 41)
      - "A Letter to Khrushchev,", 1958. (Folder 98: 42)
      - "About Rhodesia ...,", 1961. (Folder 98: 43)
      - "An Epilogue on China,", 1971. (Folder 98: 44)
      - "Dangers for the Doctors,", 1970. (Folder 98: 45)
      - "Looking Ahead,", undated. (Folder 98: 46)
      - "More Stately Mansions,", 1964. (Folder 98: 47)
      - "More Truth about Vietnam,", 1967. (Folder 98: 48)
      - "The Neutralizers,", 1963. (Folder 98: 49)
      - Interim bulletin, 1963 (Folder 98: 50)
      - "A Realistic Report ...,", 1962. (Folder 98: 51)
      - "Republics and Democracies,", 1961. (Folder 98: 52)
      - "A Timely Warning,", 1971. (Folder 98: 53)
      - "The Truth about Vietnam,", 1967. (Folder 98: 54)
      - "The Truth in Time ...,", 1966. (Folder 98: 55)
      - "Through all the Days to Be,", 1961. (Folder 98: 56)
      - "Two Revolutions at Once,", undated. (Folder 98: 57)
      - "What Is Communism?", 1970. (Folder 98: 58)
      - "What Is Money?", 1970. (Folder 98: 59)
      - "What Is the John Birch Society?", 1970. (Folder 98: 60)
      - "Which World Will It Be?", 1970. (Folder 98: 61)
      - "Wild Statements,", 1965. (Folder 98: 62-63)
    - "Why People Become Communists,", 1958. (Box-folder 99: 1)
    - "La Raza ...," Westerfield, Rex T., 1969. (Folder 99: 2)
    - "Vietnam," Wood, Wallis W., 1967. (Folder 99: 3)
  - John Day Company
    - "Out of the Depression ...," Chase, Stuart, 1931. (Folder 99: 4)
    - "Against Revolution," Seldes, Gilbert, 1932. (Folder 99: 5)
  - John T. Flynn, "The Final Secret of ...,", 1945. (Folder 99: 6)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Un-American Activities--State of Louisiana
    - "The Nation of Islam or the Muslim Cult of Islam in Louisiana,", 1963. (Folder 99: 7)
    - "Activities of the Southern Conference Educational Fund, Inc. in Louisiana," Parts I-III, 1963-1965. (Folder 99: 8)
  - Joint Publishing Company, Hong Kong--"Commemorate the 50th ...,", 1971. (Folder 99: 9)
  - Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation--"The Role of American Business ...," Moreell, Ben, 1955. (Folder 99: 10)
  - Joseph D. McGuire--"Pattern for Revolt," Read, Leonard E., 1948. (Folder 99: 11)
  - Joseph F. Albright, "The Way Out,", undated. (Folder 99: 12)
  - Judge Armstrong Foundation--"Zionist Wall Street and Third Zionist War," Armstrong, George W., 1949-1951. (Folder 99: 13)
  - K.R.P. Publications Limited
    - "British Medicine ...," Rugg-Gunn, Andrew, undated. (Folder 99: 14)
    - Douglas, C. H.
      - "Money and the Price System,", 1935. (Folder 99: 15)
      - "The Tragedy of Human Effort,", 1936. (Folder 99: 16)
        Notes for an address
  - Kamp, Joseph P., "How to Win the War ...,", undated. (Folder 99: 17)
  - Kansas Free Press—-"Kansas University Civil Rights ...,", 1965. (Folder 99: 18)
  - Karameh Reconstruction Society--"Remember Karameh,", undated. (Folder 99: 19)
  - Kegan Paul, French, Trubner and Company--"Unarmed against Fascism," Jameson, A. K., 1963. (Folder 99: 20)
  - Kenneth Goff, "Red Shadows,", 1959. (Folder 99: 21)
  - Kim Il Sung
    - "A Talk with the Delegation of the Japan Socialist Party,", 1984. (Folder 99: 22)
    - "Stadium,", 1984. (Folder 99: 23)
  - Kirkpatrick, Frank
    - "December Seven ...,", 1953. (Folder 99: 24)
    - "As I See It: McCarthy ...," and "As I See It: The Sell-out in Korea,", 1953. (Folder 99: 25)
      Messages
  - Ku Klux Klan
    - Notes, 1977 (Folder 99: 26)
    - Form letter, memorandum, and printed matter, 1928, 1969 (Folder 99: 27)
  - Klyber, Arthur B., "This Jew,", 1969. (Folder 99: 28)
  - Koch, Fred C., "A Business Man ...,", 1960. (Folder 99: 29)
  - Kohler, Herbert V., "The American Tragedy,", 1961 (Folder 99: 30)
  - Kohler Company
    - "Can a Free Economy ...," Kohler, Herbert V., 1957. (Folder 99: 31)
    - "In Freedom's Cause ...," Kohler, Herbert V. (Folder 99: 32)
  - Korean Overseas Information Service--New Year Press Conference, Chung Hee Park, 1977. (Folder 99: 33)
    Summary and full text of the conference
  - Kozina, Vladimir, "Communism as I Know It,", 1967. (Box-folder 100: 1)
  - Krieg Brothers--"Brother Cain: Red Tactics ...," Lunn, Arnold, undated. (Folder 100: 2)
  - Kullgren--"The Bible Speaks ...," Kullgren, William, 1962. (Folder 100: 3)
  - La Organizacion Continental Latinoamericana de Estudiantes (OCLAE)--"Aniversario de La,", 1976. (Folder 100: 4)
  - Labor Defender--"Karl Marx as Labor Defender," Czobel, A., and C. Kahn, 1933?. (Folder 100: 5)
  - Labor Herald Library--"The Bankruptcy ...," Foster, William. Z., 1912. (Folder 100: 6)
  - Labor Monthly--"Dialectical Materialism ...," Rudas, L., 1933. (Folder 100: 7)
  - Labor Party--"The Parable ...," Bellamy, Edward, 1933. (Folder 100: 8)
  - Labor-Progressive Party
    - "Canada's Path to ...," Buck, Tim, 1947. (Folder 100: 9)
    - "Program of ...,", undated. (Folder 100: 10)
    - "The Red Bogey," Smith, Stewart, undated. (Folder 100: 11)
  - Labor Unity Publishers--"The Trade Unions ...," Honig, Nathaniel, 1934. (Folder 100: 12)
  - Labor Party--"Labor's Peace ...," Attlee, C. R., undated. (Folder 100: 13)
  - Land-of-the-Free-Committee--"The Story Behind ...," Sammis, Ford, 1967?. (Folder 100: 14)
    History textbook
  - Lanka Sama Samaja--"The Only Road for Germany," Trotsky, Leon, 1932. (Folder 100: 15)
  - Larry Flint Publication, Free Press--"JFK Murder Solved...,", 1978. (Folder 100: 16)
  - "Last Best Hope of Earth ...," Scherman, Harry, 1941. (Folder 100: 17)
  - Lawyers Committee on Blockade--"The United Nations ...,", 1953?. (Folder 100: 18)
  - Lazarus, Ralph, "Progress, Poverty ...,", 1965. (Folder 100: 19)
  - League for Industrial Democracy
    - "American Power ...," Harrington, Michael, 1967. (Folder 100: 20)
    - Laidler, Harry W.
      - "How America Lives,", 1924. (Folder 100: 21)
      - "Public Ownership ...,", 1929. (Folder 100: 22)
    - "Looking Forward ...," Dewey, John, 1932. (Folder 100: 23)
      Discussion outlines
  - Little Listening Post, 1965. (Folder 100: 24)
  - Loucks, Vernon R., "Has Science Proved ...,", 1964. (Folder 100: 25)
  - League for Industrial Democracy
    - "European Trade Unionism ...," Neumann, Franz, 1936. (Folder 100: 26)
    - "What Is ...?" Thomas, Norman, 1925. (Folder 100: 27)
  - League for the Liberation
    - "The Devil: ...,", 1932. (Folder 100: 28)
      Program of services for the weekly assembly
    - "God: How Does ...?", 1932. (Folder 100: 29)
      Program of services for the ninth assembly
  - League of American Writers--"Harry Bridges: A Discussion ...," Trumbo, Dalton, 1941. (Folder 100: 30)
  - League of Militant Atheists--"Religion in the USSR," Yaroslavsky, E., 1932. (Folder 100: 31)
  - League of Professional Groups for Foster and Ford--"Culture and the Crisis ...,", 1932. (Folder 100: 32)
  - League of Women Voters
    - Tucson--Pima County, 1956. (Folder 100: 33)
    - United States--"The Politics of Trade,", 1971. (Folder 100: 34)
  - Learn and Live--"The True Nature of ...," Hayes, Samuel Evans, undated. (Box-folder 101: 1)
    Memorial book
  - Lefeve, B. A., "Traffic Engineering ...,", 1951. (Folder 101: 2)
  - Les Editions du Parc--"Le Vietnam ...," Tung, Tran Van, undated. (Folder 101: 3)
  - Lesse's Bureau of Anti-Jewish Information
    - "The Great Jewish ...,", undated. (Folder 101: 4)
    - "What Is this all About? Rex vs. Leese,", 1950. (Folder 101: 5)
      Report of the trial
  - Levinson, Edward, "Rise of the Auto Workers,", undated. (Folder 101: 6)
  - Liberal Publishing Company, Inc.--"Capitalism ...," Greenfield, Edward W., 1962. (Folder 101: 7-8)
  - Liberation Editions--South Vietnam
    - "Heroes and Heroines ...,", 1965. (Folder 101: 9)
    - Tho, Nguyen Huu, 1965. (Folder 101: 10)
  - Liberation
    - "Every Test Kills," Pauling, Linus, 1958. (Folder 101: 11)
  - Liberator Press--Foster, Sy
    - "The Spectre ...,", undated. (Folder 101: 12)
    - "Treasonitis ...,", undated. (Folder 101: 13)
  - Libertarian Press--"Civil Rights and Liberty,", 1964. (Folder 101: 14)
  - Liberty and Property--"First National Directory ...,", 1957. (Folder 101: 15-16)
    List of names
  - Liberty and Prosperity--"The Hybrid Race ...," Hubbard, Bela, undated. (Folder 101: 17)
  - Liberty Bell Press--"Anatomy of a ...,", 1964. (Folder 101: 18)
  - Liberty Bell Publications--"Congressman McFadden ...,", 1934. (Folder 101: 19)
  - Liberty Library--"Give Me Liberty," Lane, Rose Wilder, 1945. (Folder 101: 20)
  - Liberty Lobby
    - "America First ...,", undated. (Folder 101: 21)
    - "The EV and Charlie Show: How the GOP ...,", undated. (Folder 101: 22)
    - "A National Emergency?", undated. (Folder 101: 23)
  - Liberator Press--"The Liberator ...," Foster, Sydney H., undated. (Folder 101: 24)
  - Libyan Arab Republic Ministry of Information--"The Indian Serious ...,", 1971. (Folder 101: 25)
    Qaddafi's reply to Indira Gandhi
  - Liguorian Books--"He's a Jew," Klyber, Arthur B., 1960. (Folder 101: 26)
  - Literaturnaya Gazetta Publishers--"The Truth about American ...," Bucar, Annabelle, 1951. (Folder 101: 27)
  - Littlebooks Library--"The Poison in America's Cup," Francis, Philip, undated. (Folder 101: 28)
  - Logan, John A., "T A W H A (Big Talk),", 1954. (Folder 101: 29)
    Typescript diary
  - London District Committee Communist Party--"London Labour ...,", 1954. (Folder 101: 30)
  - London Peace News--"Tyranny ...," Sharp, Gene, undated. (Folder 101: 31)
  - Long House--"Dodd Report ...,", 1954. (Folder 101: 32)
  - Long, Hamilton, "America's ...,", 1950. (Folder 101: 33)
  - Lorain L. Morrison, "The Wedemeyer ...,", 1947. (Folder 101: 34)
  - Lory, Milton M., "World Government: ...,", 1950. (Folder 101: 35)
  - Los Angeles
    - Chamber of Commerce--The Economic Sentinel--"Bretton Woods ...," Watts, V. O., 1945. (Folder 101: 36)
    - Christian Nationalist Crusade--"The International Jew ...," Ford, Henry, Sr., undated. (Folder 101: 37)
    - Committee for Defense of the Bill of Rights--Defense, 1968. (Folder 101: 38)
      Conference journal
    - Committee for Protection of Foreign Born--"Citizens without Rights," Carlisle, Harry, undated. (Folder 101: 39)
    - City Communist Party--"How to Prepare a Report," Manuilsky, D. Z., 1946. (Folder 101: 40)
  - Louis Kirshbaum, "Respectability for Sale," and Knox, John C., "Labor-Capital and the Public,", 1940. (Box-folder 102: 1)
  - Louis B. Ward, "Business Is Business,", 1939. (Folder 102: 2)
  - Lyceum--Literature Department Workers Party of America--"ABC of Communism," Volume I, Bucharin, N., and Preobraschensky, undated. (Folder 102: 3)
  - Lyfe Production Publication--"When Mr. 666 ...," Clark, Doug, 1976. (Folder 102: 4)
  - M. Muller and K. G. Sohn--"Communism with the Mask Off," Goebbels, Joseph, undated. (Folder 102: 5)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1951. (Folder 102: 6)
  - McBirnie, William Steuart--Booklets
    - "Capitalism, Christianity and Common Sense!" "The Truth about the ...," and "How Communism Can Be Destroyed!", 1961, undated. (Folder 102: 7)
    - "The Immorality of the New Left, undated. (Folder 102: 8)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, "The Party of Betrayal,", undated. (Folder 102: 9)
  - Maco Magazine Corporation--"Way to Happiness ...," Sheen, Fulton J., 1953. (Folder 102: 10)
  - McGregor, A. H., "Has the Methodist Church ...?", 1961. (Folder 102: 11)
  - Magazine Publishers Association--"America's Stake ...,", 1956. (Folder 102: 12)
    Summary of conference discussion
  - Magazine War Guide, 1944 January - February. (Folder 102: 13)
    Monthly summary of war information
  - Manning, John R., "The Story of Old Glory,", 1960. (Folder 102: 14)
  - Martin, Margie M., "Shun-Human ...,", 1971. (Folder 102: 15)
  - Maricopa Advisory Council--"Are these Authors in your Library?", undated. (Folder 102: 16)
    List of authors of books
  - Marilyn R. Allen
    - "Open Letter ...,", 1962. (Folder 102: 17)
    - "America at the Crossroads ...,", undated. (Folder 102: 18)
    - "For Freedom's Sake,", 1950. (Folder 102: 19)
    - "Fortify Alaska ...,", 1948. (Folder 102: 20)
    - "A Jewish Friend ...,", 1947. (Folder 102: 21)
    - "Jewish Protocols,", 1946. (Folder 102: 22)
    - "Judaic-Communism ...,", 1946. (Folder 102: 23)
    - "The Only Way Out,", undated. (Folder 102: 24)
    - "Operation Scuttling of America,", 1947. (Folder 102: 25)
      Textbook
    - "Peace-Mongering ...,", 1946. (Folder 102: 26)
    - "White-hating Dictators ...,", 1962. (Folder 102: 27)
    - "Whose Country Is This?", 1947. (Folder 102: 28)
  - Marx Institute of America--"Was Marx Wrong?" Rubinow, I. M., 1914. (Folder 102: 29)
  - Marxian Educational Society--"Left Wing ...," Lenin, N., 1921. (Folder 102: 30)
  - Marzani and Munsell--"War and Peace ...," Neal, Fred Warner, 1961. (Folder 102: 31)
  - Masses and Mainstream
    - "America's Racist Laws," Aptheker, Herbert, 1951. (Folder 102: 32)
    - "I Take My Stand for Peace," Du Bois, W. E. B., 1951. (Folder 102: 33)
  - Mass Exchange of Youth Plan (MEP)--"To Win the Cold War ...,", 1946. (Folder 102: 34)
    Excerpts from speech
  - Match--"Anarchism ...," Woodworth, Fred, 1973. (Folder 102: 35)
  - Matthews, Marcia, "Strike a Blow for Human Liberty!" (Folder 102: 36)
  - Meador Publishing Company--"Lightning over ...," Elsom, John R., 1941. (Folder 102: 37)
  - "Meet Nelson Rockefeller,", 1958. (Folder 102: 38)
  - Melechinsky, Andrew, "Constitutional Revival,", 1985. (Box-folder 103: 1)
  - Melman, Seymour, "A Strategy for American Security ...,", 1963. (Folder 103: 2)
  - "Malcolm X ...," Breitman, George, 1965. (Folder 103: 3)
  - "How Cuba ...," Ring, Harry, 1969. (Folder 103: 4)